# AJANI KOFOWOROLA

## Frontend developer

07045245035 • kofoworolaajani1@gmail.com • 25, lyke Meregini Street, Bucknor Estate, Ejigbo, Lagos state. • https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajani-kofoworola-taiwo-005468240

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Talented and experienced front-end developer with 3+ years of experience executing with diverse skills. Experience has taught me to take accessibility and responsiveness seriously, and I am excited to continue my career with a focus on making web developments easily accessible, completely responsive, and intuitive for users

#### **Skills**

communication | Excellent time management skills | Public

speaking | Cross-cultural

Technical Skills HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Git & Version control | React | Tailwind |

WordPress | Elementor

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Front-End developer

Digitaldesign247 | August 2023 - Current

- Creating and maintaining the user interface and user experience of websites or web applications.
- Writing and optimizing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript code to ensure responsive and visually appealing web pages.
- Ensuring that websites work well on various devices and screen sizes, using techniques like responsive design and mobile-first development.

• Effectively communicating with team members to understand the project requirements and provide updates.

### Front-End Developer Westhill Estate Limited | Lagos State, Nigeria | August 2021 - Current

- Writing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to create and maintain web pages and applications.
- Updating their products on the site.
- Participating in team meetings and discussions to understand project requirements and provide updates on our progress.
- Wrote 100% maintainable code with tests

#### **WordPress Developer**

Ten Kings Limited | August 2021 - November 2021

- Evaluated the structure and design of 30+ web pages.
- Developed 20+ new features to enhance user experience.
- Continuously learning about WordPress updates and best practices to improve your development skills.
- Developed 9+ websites for internal project design management.
- Created Elementor UX designs that satisfied business objectives and user needs.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

- AWARD ENVIRONMENTAL PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR
  University Of Bowen University, Iwo, Osun State
- AWARD OF SERVICE- VICE PRESIDENT

THE National ASSOCIATION OF COMPUTING STUDENTS

ACHIEVEMENT- MENTOR

University Of Bowen University, Iwo, Osun State

#### **EDUCATION**

Bowen University, Iwo, Osun State (2019-2023)

Course of study: Computer and Information Technology (Second-class upper-division)

Excel College, Ejigbo Lagos state.

Secondary School Certificate Examination (2018)

• Focal Point Nursery and primary school New yidi road, Ilorin

First School Leaving Certificate

### **HOBBIES**

- Environmental conservation
- Art
- Cooking
- Travel

## **Training**

• Digital Art library Flip to Tech

Frontend web development with the certificate

August 2022

• Digital Art library Flip to Tech

UI/UX with the certificate

November 2022

#### **REFEREES**

• Mr. Ajani Afolabi

07061190254

25, lyke Meregini Street, Bucknor Estate, Ejigbo, Lagos state.

• Mrs. Ajani Adekemi

08062718214

25, lyke Meregini Street, Bucknor Estate, Ejigbo, Lagos state.